Let's take off this uniform and be free
When will we stop shedding tears?
Hello everyone, I'm Iroha Okuda, a freshman at Nogizaka46!
Ta-da!
It's kind of a knightly feeling, isn't it?
So, this is the second street live show!
Yay!
Let me tell you where I'll be this time
Ta-da!
Machida Station!
Here we are in Machida!
As you can see...
There are not many people here.
I'm a little worried about what's going to happen.
I'm a little worried about how it's going to turn out.
I've been trying to make it fun for the guests
I'm not sure if we'll be able to get enough people to show up.
I'm a little nervous about whether we'll be able to get a good turnout, but
I'm not sure if we'll be able to get a good turnout, but we'll have fun while doing it.
I'll do my best.
Last time I sat on a chair.
But this time, I'm going to sit on the ground.
I'm going to do it on the ground this time.
I've brought a thing to put on my butt.
I'm so excited!
What's different from last time?
And there are exquisitely few people and exquisitely many people!
What am I going to do?
When I saw the venue...
Is this it? Is this it? Is this it? I was like...
Even if people don't show up, it's okay because you'll all be there.
That's what I'm going to do.
I really don't know what to do.
I don't know what to do.
But it's okay, because it was the same last time.
I drew this, but it's okay, because it was like that last time.
I painted this
Thank you for coming so close.Thank you for coming so close.
I'm Iroha Okuda.
Now let's see if anyone comes near here.
Looking good.
Oh, man, I'm so nervous.
Tune it out for a second.
There's really no one here. Say goodbye to JK's sword.
I can't let my youth get the best of me
I'm walking on my own two feet, it's no wonder I don't know what I'm doing
It's okay if you don't know how to do it
Someone always had a hand out for me
I'm starting to feel suffocated in this environment
It's okay if you don't know yet
When you grow up, you'll understand
Being overprotected like that
That's what's ruining me right now
I don't care if I get hurt, I just want you to treat me like an adult
I want to face the reality of it all without turning away
Let's take off this uniform and be free
Say goodbye to my JK sword
I don't need to wear the armor of innocence
Come on, don't be bound by common sense, illuminated by the light of youth
I'll walk straight down the path I believe in
Come on, don't be bound by common sense, every smile and tear is a treasure
No matter what happens, it's a page
To live is to drink and drink over, thank you very much
I sang a song called “Take off the Uniform and Say Sayonara
I sang a song called “Take Off Your Uniform and Say Goodbye” and not many people showed up
I'm so embarrassed.
It's a little embarrassing
Thank you very much.
I graduated from high school this past March.
I took off my uniform and said goodbye.
So I sang this song.
I'm so excited.
Well, if it's true...
Next, I was thinking of asking you guys to help me sing it.
I don't know what I'll do. I don't know what to do.
Will you help me?
Um, well, I'm here alone. I was just passing by.
Come here for a moment.
Do you know Nogizaka?
Yes, I know Nogizaka.
I went to one of their concerts.
Thank you very much.
I'm so glad.
Is it on TV or something?
Yes, it's on YouTube.
It's on YouTube.
Nogizaka is streaming.
That's right.
We did a street live once before.
We did a second one today.
I'm so glad I'm lucky I did a street show once before, and I was doing the second one today.
I'm so lucky.
I'm so happy.
I wanted to ask you to clap for the next song.
Yes, okay.
Please do.
Then, please imitate me. Cha-cha-chi. Please, my true feelings are always hidden from everyone.
Swept away by fate.
Where did our paths cross? Our hearts were far apart
What should I shout out loud
Love ends so easily like this
Goodbye Stay with me
A little more Don't leave me
Look at me hard to say
Don't let go Stay with me
Please cause I love you
One more kiss
Give me one more kiss for eternity stay with me
I'm a little nervous
I'm sorry, thank you.
I'm so nervous.
Hello. Hello.
Hi. - Hi.
Thank you for stopping by.
Let's sing the next song.
When I first joined Nogizaka.
When I joined Nogizaka... they made a documentary about me.
I sang in it once.
I don't know why I'm so nervous today.
I'm going to sing it... and I'm going to cry... even now, the days are shining brightly
You'll never get joy and sorrow again
I was just climbing up the hill without knowing anything and suddenly I realized I was here, blowing snow and saying goodbye to the sky
Turn the town into a pure white world
The familiar paths I've walked until today
And the scenery of everyday life
Touch the snow, it's still beautiful
I have no regrets
To be reborn as a new me
I want it all to disappear
Standing in the circle of time
I'm murmuring now to the circle of time saying thank you
Thank you
I'm nervous
Okay, we're going to have a vote.
I don't know what I'm going to do.
I guess I really haven't practiced.
One second before despair.
It's okay to cry
Love in a roundabout way
I Hope I Never Forget
Kigekitakatta kigekitakatta
Trigger
It's okay to cry
Here's a chance
Okay, I'll sing this song as a trigger
A little water.
Wait a minute, you really haven't practiced
Wait a minute, please Wait a minute, please.
In the middle of the intersection.
Then I'll take more, please.
Cute.
I get anxious in the middle of an intersection, wondering how long that light will stay blue.
It starts blinking unexpectedly, like it's rushing me.
Before I knew it, I was walking a little faster.
As if it didn't matter what I wanted.
Everyone is running at the same time, everyone is running at the same time.
What is it that they're in such a hurry to catch up with?
I'm looking at it objectively. I hate it when my light heart is triggered not by logic, but by the impulse in my chest.
It always starts with this impulse in my heart.
To be swept away is to resist.
To live is to make only one choice
Look, someone in the crowd starts running
Like they've been hooked on it, everyone's running like they've been hooked on it
Everyone starts to run like they've been caught in a river
I can't make up my mind and I need something to push me
I want something to push me forward Kikkake kikkake light hearted kikkake is not a logical trigger
It always starts with this impulse in my heart
To be swept away, that's the intention
I like it.
To live is to choose the day when you choose to have a headache.
Let's live as we are
Let's live as we are.
You're so cute.
How old is he?
Five?
Kindergarten?
Elementary school?
You don't go to school?
Me neither.
Oh, I see.
Thank you. Me too? The haiku section? I see. Thank you.
You said earlier, it's okay to cry.
Let's do it. That person you've been longing for has already moved away, or that promise you made that day has been forgotten.
One word, no one is listening.
The glamorous show window I saw in a magazine The glamorous show window you saw in a magazine
Or drowned in the marks of someone's hand that was peeking in.
I'd rather not want what I wanted
Is worse than giving up.
I think it's unfortunate
To know both the dream and the reality
Knowing both
I think it's better to live strong
And live strong
Is life.
When did we stop crying?
We're not stronger than we were when we were little, and we're not sadder than we'll ever be.
But we grit our teeth and hold it in.
But it's okay to cry once in a while
When did we stop crying?
We're not stronger than we were when we were young
We're not stronger than we were when we were little
Even when we grow up, there are still sad things
I clench my teeth against the bamboo and leaves and try to hold it in.
Thank you very much. How was it?
Thank you. Have a safe trip home.
Thank you, thank you.
Thank you very much.
That's the end of the street performance.
Today was a surprise.
I was so nervous because I was surprised myself.
I was a little...
I'm not very good at it.
And the guitar.
I messed up a little bit.
I put a lot of emotion into it.
We even had some cute customers.
What a town! It's a nice town.
It's a town! It was a nice town!
When I can do it again someday
I would like to come back with more power and
I would like to communicate with everyone more
I would like to communicate more with everyone and make it more participatory. I'll always be thinking about which songs would be good so that we can have a kind of participatory type of thing.
I'll keep thinking about which songs would be good.
Thank you very much for watching!
Please subscribe to our channel and give us a rating!
See you soon!
you